高清电影网 http://M1080.com 提供字幕下载
那是胡安獭
That's Juancho.
@房子真大。
The house is huge.
是的，我小的r候可]@么大。
Yeah
最后一次修葺的是巧夏情g房，
The last things they built were the rooms upstairs
后面是桑拿房、O可意水流按摩浴缸
and in the back
和按摩房。
the massage room.
- 嗯~真棒！           - 很不e。超舒服的。
- Wow! That's great! - It's amazing. Very relaxing.
我爸曾建了厝B池和戒康椭行摹
At one point my dad set up a spa and a rehabilitation center for smokers.
嗯~
很多
A Lot of
真害。
That's great.
Γ很多人恚他斫，@里待上一周。
Yeah
- 一W球龊陀境亍 - 太好了！
- A tennis court and pool. - That's great!
他周六晚上淼...
Two of them came on Saturday night...
白w色的那，R克西，有托米。他睡在那骸
Maxi
那里是迭戈。
And there's Diego.
好幔M德？
Fede! Is everything alright?
- 你好吧？
- How are you?
- 你好。- 我是赫曼，很高d到你。
-Hi
- 你睡好幔
- Did you sleep well?
好，但我很晚才上床。R毯婉R克西，我熬夜到很久。
Yeah
我吸嗨了。
I was really stoned.
我神志不清的。
We were wasted.
互相嘲笑著Ψ健
We were laughing our heads off.
我最后到了泳池。
We ended up in the pool.
胡安也乎乎的，
And Juan
把迭戈扔M了池子。
threw Diego into the pool.
- 不吧！他肯定牧恕 - 是的，穿著衣服被扔下去的。
- No! He must've been pissed. - Yeah
我X得手C也在他身上е。
I think he even had his cell phone on him.
太了！
No way!
真的，我X得是。因樗真的胡安很。
Yeah
他都火冒三丈了，我so溜了。
我可不想惹上麻。
I didn't want any trouble.
@就是@里最典型的一天。
That's a typical day here.
Γ那是真的。
Yeah
你要R黛茶是咖啡？
Do you want mate or coffee?
- 我要他去看看房g，然后我再到窍氯デ魄啤
- I'm going to show him the room and then we'll come downstairs.
- ΑＪ牵是的。
- Alright.Yes. Yeah.
嘿，老兄，穿l泳或者e的什么子。
Hey
@家伙老是整天不穿到走。
This guy goes around naked all day.
再。
Nice to meet you.
嗨，可好啊。
Hi
- 嗨，@是赫曼。       - 你好，迭戈。
- Hi
都好幔
Is everything alright?
不。我去巧仙洗筇，因e的所全都塞M了I吐物。
No
- 其他都是？ - ΓΑ
- There too? - Yeah
R趟前吐的到都是
Lucho threw up before going to sleep and it's still there...
胡}卜和那些|西全在那骸
pieces of carrot and everything.
我你磉@里放松滋欤
And I told you to come here to relax for a few days
看上去可不像@周的。
but that doesn't seem to be the plan for this weekend.
你坐火淼模
Did you come by train?
是的，旅途很棒。我很喜g。
Yeah
- 是真的，我也坐火淼摹   - 我]坐^火。
- Yeah
- 他f很不e。    - 的_。
- They say it's great. - Yeah.
- 你吃早餐了幔   - ]。M德在泡R黛茶。
- Did you guys have breakfast? - No
我他去房g看看。
I'm going to show him his room
然后我再下沓栽绮汀
and then we'll come down for breakfast.
- 好幔 - 好，]}。
- Okay? - Okay
xx。
Thanks.
- 你在吃什么，Fatso？   - u蛋，我I了。
- What are you eating
怎么了？
What's up?
我做了很棒很清晰的簟
I just had an awesome lucid dream.
- “清晰”是什么意思？        - 跟真的一樱太像真的了。
- What does "lucid" mean? - That it's real. It's very real.
舻绞裁戳耍
What did you dream?
我在蒂格雷（阿根廷|北部城），我姐姐家，
I was in Tigre
靠近河。
next to the river.
我不知道我在干什么，和l在一起，但我知道我在那里。
I don't know what I was doing
然后？
And?
[O是]，房子，后院的烤架。
Everything was the same
不知楹挝易吡诉M去，上了恰
I don't know why I went inside and went up the stairs.
我上了三恰
I went up three floors.
我X得@是平房。
But I think it's a one-story house.
- 什么？ - 我J槟鞘鞘平房。
- What?   - I think it's a one-story house.
我M入走廊r，
And when I got to the terrace
水的位置已虻搅岁_高度。
the water was at the level of the balcony.
很多的水，很多。
There was a lot of water.
就好像一百a外就有l瀑布似的。
It was as if there were a waterfall a hundred yards away.
@影
Yeah.
可我已上了
But I had gone up two floors
所以不可能那么高
so there couldn't be water on both levels
然后我就意R到只是簟
So then I realized it was a dream.
等我意R到的r候，感X就像是做了...
And whenever I realize that
我_始走，我知道我可以即刻醒^怼
so I started walking
我^了一座颉
I passed a bridge.
我走M了一有吧_的地方，像g俱凡俊
I went inside this place with bars
我旋即和第一眼到的小妞H崞怼
And I started making out with the first chick I saw.
我扒去她的衣服。
I took off her clothes
我_始吮吸她的乳^，她下面可真硬。
I started sucking her tits and her pussy really hard.
@小妞就那诱驹谀抢铩
And the chick just stood there.
衾镱^那些人物突然o止不恿耍你明白吧？
You know like in dreams when the characters suddenly stop moving?
- 知道，很怪。   - Α
- Yeah
有那么一刻，她的道得跟沙似的。
And at one point
然后地，我就醒了。
and... bam! I got up.
我_眼，望著天花板。心想“死”！
I opened my eyes and looked at the ceiling. I thought "Damn it!"
可糁的r候真爽。
But it was cool while it lasted.
沙子的部分可把我著了。
The part about the sand freaked me out.
正是
Yeah.
可我仍能w味到她的下w，太真了。
But it was so real that I can still taste her pussy.
- 真是美簦 - L起矸勰鄱嘀，可口十足！
- Sweet!     - It was really pink and delicious!
- 我得叫些姑娘^怼   - 我需要她，不是幔
- We have to call some girls over. - We need it
Yeah.
好吧
Alright.
- R里W兄弟不是赢，兄弟。   - 就是赢
- Mario Bros isn't a cartoon
不，老兄，你昨天就]明白我f的。
No
R里W兄弟不是赢。
Mario Bros isn't a cartoon.
你f是，我f不是。
You guys said it was and I said it wasn't.
那就是我X得不是的原因。
That's why I think I didn't lose.
那你看^R里W的赢？
Did you used to watch Mario Bros cartoons?
那]差e，就跟赢一印
It's the same thing. It's like a cartoon.
你就是不肯承J你了，因槟]猜中。
You just can't admit that you lost because you couldn't guess
F在你f，如果我告V你不是赢的，
and now you're saying that if we had told you it wasn't a cartoon
你就猜中了。
you would've guessed
然后你f它就是某N赢。
and then you would've said that it's a kind of cartoon.
行了吧，迭戈。我不了解你！
Come on
看看你有多。
See how competitive you are?
我]法不在意，你才是好俚哪人！
I couldn't care less! You're the one who's competitive!
我很反感e人把演T、人民
I hate it when people mix up the actors
和角色混淆在一起。
with characters.
一次Fatso到了杰克・斯伯洛
One time Fatso got Jack Sparrow
他你是不是演Tr，你f是。
and when he asked if it was an actor
e！s翰尼・德普才是演T。
No! The actor's Johnny Depp.
（《加勒比海I》杰克船L）
杰克・斯帕_只是海I的位。
- “只是海I的位”？ - Γ
- "Worked as a pirate"? - Yeah!
行行行，F在成了海I是位了。
Now being a pirate's a job.
你不去理解我e的例子的r候，我真的又庥钟你。
I hate it when you don't understand the example. It pisses me off.
你太好倭恕
You're so competitive.
行了，迭戈。
Come on
Fatso，你看M了？
Hey
Fatso
Fatso!
@妞涸谖工作r跟我{情
The chick flirts with me when we're all working...
然后我玩欲擒故v。
and then she plays hard-to-get.
- 我是指... - 怎玩法？
- I mean... - Like how?
我去帕勃_的住。你知道那Ll的家伙吧？
We were going to Pablo's house. You know the guy with long hair?
知道
Yeah.
好，帕勃_、阿古斯、那小妞和我。
Okay
帕勃_和阿古斯去I啤酒，
Pablo and Agus went to buy some beer
我就和那姑娘。
and the girl and I were alone.
我挨著她坐著，因樗想透露o我一些息，
I sat next to her because she wanted to show me a message
那姑娘把她龅募绨^怼
and the girl gave me the cold shoulder.
她龅酶冰似的。她去^了浴室。
She was cold as ice. She went to the bathroom.
她老是那拥呐e樱癔Y似的。
She always act like that
隔天工作r，著所有人的面，
The next day at work
她走M砦橇宋遥o我按摩脖i。
she walked in
她是做同一件事。
She always does the same thing.
了
She's crazy.
e聊她了。
Forget about her.
有事？
Yeah.
- 你^M幔       - ]到。
- Have you guys seen Fer?  - No.
所以呢？
So?
你_定那姑娘不缘媚阌信友？
Are you sure the girl doesn't know you're in a relationship?
_定
Yes.
女孩能lF那些事骸
Girls find out about those things.
她不可能知道。
There's no way she could know.
我也不X得他告V她，因樗都知道我想干她。
And I don't think the guys told her
Right.
]事骸
It's okay.
可你有女朋友啊。
But you have a girlfriend.
各有所邸
To each his own.
- 我找到了@。 - 好啊。
- I found this one. - Yeah.
但快用完了。
But it's almost empty.
蚊子都快咬死我了。
The mosquitoes are killing me.
你也...
Here you go...
我一到@里，它就在咬我了。
As soon as I came in they started to bite me too.
咬得你全身都是！
They bit you all over!
看@...
Look here...
不吧，老兄！
No way
咬得到都是！
They bit me all over!
@里
Here
有@骸
And here too.
就像我f的
As I was saying
迭戈和胡安是JR最久的。
Diego and Juan the longest.
我挠@就JR了。
I've know them since we were in kindergarten.
我都是很要好的朋友。
But we're all very good friends.
其余的是后碚JR的。
We met the rest later on.
在小W，我JR了R獭⒗W和托米。
In primary school
R克西曾和托米的妹妹^邸
And Maxi used to go out with Tomi's sister.
^去他常和我踢足球。
He used to play soccer with us all the time
所以我才uu和他熟j起怼
so we started getting along really well with him.
我七年JR的Fatso。
And we met Fatso in eleventh grade.
他是留了5次是6次。我f跑偏了。
I think he had failed five or six times. We lost track.
也是，你能看出硭老一些。
Yeah
今天你看不到圣地哥，
And you're not going to meet Santiago today
因樗遇一西班牙女孩，搬去西班牙了。
because he moved to Spain when he met a Spanish girl here.
每2到3月回恚
He used to come back every two or three months
但他回淼拇担越碓缴倭恕
but then he started coming here less frequently.
我X得他F在也不回恚
I don't think he'd come back now
如果2年前他]回淼脑。
if he didn't come back two years ago.
Leg
Leg...
你好
Hi.
那...我去泳池了。
Well
你和M鹂帐值溃是吧？
You do karate with Fer
@不是空手道，蠢。
It's not karate
- f的是同|西。 - 才不是同|西。
- It's the same thing. - It's not the same thing.
是，我曾^空手道，但我搬去Adrogué后，
Yeah
{\pos(1306
我就_始W跆拳道了，因槟旱娜硕季它。
I started doing taekwondo
把它做某N\砭。
I did it to do some kind of sport.
我不太喜g，也]腰В]到什么等。
I don't like it that much. I don't have a belt or anything.
我不知道是否能@得更高e的腰А
I don't know if I'm going to get different color belts.
你在圣R丁V龅某嘏暇瓢晒ぷ鳎
You work at the pool bar at San Martin Square
是的
Yeah.
有一天我看你和M在那海Π桑
We saw you there one day with Fer
Γ我就在那里遇的。
Yeah
我就_始聊起恚
We started talking a lot
他我碓，
and he told me to try out the club
我就成朋友了。
so we became friends.
你W^其他|西幔
Are you studying anything?
我W^建筑，后矸了。
I used to study architecture and I dropped out.
- 在那海 - 拉普拉塔。
- Where?   - In La Plata.
- 不e嘛！ - 是的，我喜g...
- Nice!      - Yeah
我喜g，
I like to draw
我更愿意似漫的插。
but I'd rather draw things like comic book illustrations...
真正的作。
Real drawings.
不管怎樱我是想靠砩活。
So anyway... I'd love to draw for a living.
可很yふ业竭@NP。
But it's very hard to find the right connections.
- M有超大的漫集。                 - 是的。
- Fer has a big comic book collection. - Yeah.
你看^]？很大！
Have you guys seen it? It's huge!
看^
Yeah.
- 我能去抽根？ - 去吧。
- Should I roll a blunt? - Please.
]事，抽吧。
Yeah
嘿，怎樱X得好幔
Hey
田里的守望者
THE CATCHER IN THE RYE
很好看幔
Are you enjoying it?
很棒。
It's awesome.
他是ゴ蟮淖骷摇
He's a great writer.
的_。
Yeah
你干嘛啊，兄弟！
What are you doing
R蹋你就是Z！
Lucho
我也怕Fatso。
I'd be scared of Fatso too.
老兄，e太^分。@又不是世界杯。
Yeah
你踢得太狠了。
You kick too hard.
我f^不打得你落花流水，你太弱了。
I said I'm not gonna beat you up because you're weak
要是你^m┪业脑，我打得你都J不出怼
but if you keep bothering me
你朋友周六到底聿恚
So are your friends coming here on Saturday or not?
你是b作很忠的幼印
You always act like you're faithful
s心急如焚想到那些女孩。算什么？
but you're dying to meet those girls. What the hell?
你可真基！
You're So gay!
]嘴吧！
Shut up!
e跟基佬似的！
Don't be gay!
我只是想到美好事物T了。
I just want some eye candy
她幔
But are they coming?
看到@里只有我八人r，她早早跑掉的。
When they saw there were eight of us
卡f她不恚
Well
可要是我k派Γ她就和朋友一起怼
but if we throw a party
前滋煳八Ω端。
The other day
不可能我每人搞一。
There can't be two of us for each.
@可不像是去拍成人片。
It's not like we're going to make porn.
- 但是胡安上了她中的一。  - Α
- But Juan screwed one of them. - Yeah.
她可不是性色的人。
They're no prudes.
我]上另外一是因樗知道我有女友。
I didn't screw the other one because she knows I have a girlfriend
而且我已做了。
otherwise
完完全全
Totally.
- 你I巧克力牛奶了幔        - I了。
- Did you buy chocolate milk? - Yeah.
嘿，赫曼，你有ο罅幔
Hey
他是M的男友。
He's Fer's boyfriend.
嫉妒了，你@吮u巴的娘？
Are you jealous
我紊怼
No
如果我L得像布拉德・皮特的，
If I looked like Brad Pitt
女孩像挑逗他一硖舳何摇
and girls hit on me like they probably hit on this guy
直到我四十q都不停止和她y搞。
I wouldn't stop fooling around until I'm in my forties
然后我才_始考]一段真正的感情P系。
and then I'd start thinking about a relationship.
你老是想要一女友，然后和}P混欺_她。
You always want a girlfriend to cheat on her with sluts.
@里唯一忠的人的是托R斯。
The only faithful guy here is Tomas.
我也很忠\，好帷
I'm pretty faithful too
是，是。Α
Yeah
女孩也同又邑，才不是那印
It's not like girls are faithful either.
我一c阂膊恍拧
I don't believe that at all.
然不是。她就跟我一樱甚至更糟。
Of course not. They're just like us
她狡猾O了。
They're just really sly.
她能e幸逃，你永hlF不了。
They get away with it and you never find out.
我不清楚@家伙的想法。
I don't know what's up with the guy.
我只知道他]女朋友。
What I do know is that he doesn't have a girlfriend.
我]造。
I'm not making it up
槭裁此邀我？
Why did he invite me?
我不知道。
I don't know.
你在@旱脑肯定炸裂的。
Your head would explode if you were here.
他老是光著身子走碜呷ァ
They walk around naked all the time.
今天他我是不是有ο罅恕
Hey
我f]有。
and I said no.
不，我]fe。
No
他]我有]有女朋友。
They didn't ask me if I had a girlfriend.
不，我]fe。
No
M就那么著。
And Fer was just listening.
你是傻幔
Are you stupid?
M就是那人。
Fer's the guy.
要是姑娘磉@海他又上了她中的一，那我就完蛋了。
If some chicks come here and he screws one of them
Yeah.
我不知道，我要待在在@骸
I don't know. I'm just going to stay here.
我^mb傻，看看他怎印
I'm going to play dumb for a while and see what he does.
我不知道。
I don't know.
你太蠢了。
You're so stupid.
好了，拜，拜。
Okay
拜拜
Bye.
你好
Hi.
- 你好幔      - 挺好。
- How are you? - Fine.
那就好
Great.
很抱歉打你，我要自助烤，
Sorry to bother you
可我]有蠹。
and we don't have any newspapers.
- 你有蠹幔                   - 有，然有。
- Do you have any? - Yeah
- 真的有？   - 我o你拿^怼
- Really? - I'll bring you some.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
嗨
Hi.
- Hi.
- 你好幔      - 好。
- How are you? - Fine.
- 你人挺多的哈。             - 是的。
- There are so many of you. - Yeah.
- 天獠诲e哈？        - Α
- Nice weather
女孩怎么樱
How are the girls?
挺好的
Fine.
你她擦上防袼，日光太烈人的。
You should make them wear sunscreen. The sun's really burning.
是的，我知道。可她F在在屋里待著呢。
Yeah
而且她晚上睡不著。
otherwise they can't get to sleep at night.
他砹恕
There he is.
- @些蛄耍   - 是的，太好了。
- Is this enough? - Yeah
- 蛄耍 - xx。
- Yeah? - Thanks.
如果需要，就跟我f。
If you need more
- 好的，xx。 -再。
- Okay
再，伙。再。
'Bye
她真可郏
She was cute!
真可郏
Really cute!
你投o了e的人，承J吧。
You voted for the wrong guy
不知道，我φ治]啥概念。
I don't know. I have no idea about politics.
我就不告V你。
I shouldn't have even told you.
假如你不了解，就。
If you have no idea
我不是f你就必得理解，
I'm not saying you have to understand
可你@么大人，不就那么S便投了。
but you're old enough to not vote for just anyone.
你]x好度假的地方。
You're not choosing where you're going to go on vacation.
Π桑
Right?
有一大堆好玩的地方。
There's a whole bunch of stuff at play.
你咨一下我，或者你爸爸。
You should've asked me about it
好吧，]你爸爸。
Well
你下周的人。
But you should've asked around a little
至少你知道你在ol投票。
so at least you know what you're voting for.
或者...你]戴套上一女孩，
Or would you screw a girl without a condom
HH是因樗f她服了避孕？
just because she says she's on the pill?
得看她有多惹火了。
It depends how hot she is.
- 那是糟糕的例子。     - 槭裁矗
- But that's a bad example.  - Why?
因槟阏f你信任@女孩。
Because you supposedly trust the girl.
你X得她不向你撒e。
You don't think she's gonna lie to you.
可是如果你投o了e的人，
But if you vote for the wrong person
你最后只能接受。
you end up taking it up the butt.
他f要o你背部按摩，
They say they're gonna give you a back massage
最后s插到你屁股里。
and they end up sticking it up your butt.
要是他插M你屁股里，那就@樱
If they stick it up your butt
因槟阆敫惺芩插在里^的快感。
because you want to feel it inside.
嘿，你看上去真像阿根廷人。
Hey
什么意思？
What do you mean?
- 你看上去像什么？    - 西班牙的。
- What do you look like? - Spanish.
我呢？
And me?
法人。你需要的只是雷帽和刷。
French. All you need is a beret and a paintbrush.
那我呢？
What about me?
意大利人
Italian.
Fatso像俄人。
Fatso looks Russian.
托米像阿拉伯人。
Tomas looks Arabian.
里W像德人，迭戈像瑞典人。
Leo looks German and Diego looks Swedish.
我像哪人？
What do I look like?
你像英人。
You look English.
你看起砭拖裼足球\T。
You look like an English soccer player.
1，2，3，4，5，6，7，8，9，10
One
17，18
29，30！
twenty-nine
你怎么@影。坷鲜窃谧鞅祝
What's the matter with you? You're always cheating!
- 怎么回事？          - 你到音了幔
- What happened? - Did you hear that?
你是作弊，伙！
You're always cheating
你不能那油妫
You can't play like that!
住手！
Stop!
里W，住手！
Stop it
你白V！
You moron!
你叫l白V呢？
Who are you calling a moron?
他就是蠢！他一直作弊！我不能再@么玩下去！
He's an idiot! He keeps cheating! I can't play like this!
- 住手，里W。 - e激印
- Stop it
住手！
Stop it!
住手，里W！
Stop
@不是\速，你太J真了。
It's not a championship. You get too worked up.
那我槭裁催要玩？
Then why are we playing?
你e激樱你也是！
Take it easy! And you too!
我要得分了。
I'm gonna score.
把f^恚兄弟。就你自己抽哦。
Pass the blunt
e生猓伙。
Don't get upset
我只是玩游颍你s真的怒了。
We were just playing and you got really pissed off!
可我玩r你s作弊，那d懒恕Ｄ悴荒苣幼樱
But if we're playing and you cheat
- e@么婆娘似的磨\！ - 你扯些什么y七八糟|西，混球？
- Stop being such a pussy! - What are you talking about
- 我就是鬼混打lrg而已！           - 你就是混蛋，伙。
- We were just fooling around for a while! - You're a jerk
操你大的。
Go fuck yourself!
o卓凇
Let me have some.
日混球...
Mother fucker...
{\fs50\pos(936
米_・R{拉
Milo Manara.
Milo Manara?
你不JR他？
Don't you know him?
他是意大利人...
He's an Italian...
一天才。我爸爸有一堆他的漫。
A genius. My dad had a bunch of his comic books.
前兹哲铰和我去了派Γ
The other day Flor and I went to a party
{\fs48\pos(1002
M是同性俚谋勇≈髁x者...你缘盟是激M分子吧？
full of gay Peronists... You know she's an activist there?
嗯~
我盯著最基的那家伙看，穿著@身r衣。
And I looked like the gayest guy in there
我v真的。根本]人砀我搭。
I'm serious. No one gave me the time of day.
他焊翰豢茨恪＞褪悄印
They don't even look at you.
等等
Wait...
好，可是，你F在在哪里？
Okay
是，很明@，兄弟。
Yeah
Γ可就待在加油站，一半小r我就到。
Yeah. But stay thereat the gas station. I'll be there in half an hour.
行幔
Okay?
好...好的，老兄，好！
Yeah... Alright
R克西
Maxi...
R克西，跟我去接Fatso。
Maxi
他和胡安。那女孩把他甩你在那里了。
He's with Juan. The girls left him there.
他去了另一派Α
They went to another party.
R克西...
Maxi...
咋了？他做了？
What? Did they have sex?
Fatsof他做了。他在浴室上了她。
Fatso said he did. He screwed her in a bathroom.
胡安]能。他只和她在院子里H崃讼隆
But Juan didn't. He just made out with her in the yard.
so的，兄弟，我走。
Come on
- 我累死了，老兄。 - 快c，多替e人著想些！
- I'm exhausted
e┪遥兄弟！
Stop bothering me
- so的，so！ - 好！
- Come on
走了。
Let's go.
著，F在你到外面去玩足球，
Listen
Andrea泶撸好帷
and let Andrea clean up
]}，但是M德在躺著，他有c不舒服。
Okay
他不K事的。
But he won't get in the way.
之，她不用打吣情g房就行了。
In any case
然可以，]}。
Of course
{眼睛那男孩是l？
Who? The boy with the blue eyes?
赫曼，我一跆拳道的朋友。
German
他磉^我家状巍Ｄ阋^他吧？
He came to our house several times. You've seen him
^，可我不知道他是不是e人的朋友。
Yeah
不是，他是我朋友。但是我他一人怼
No
因樗就要和一些朋友去南方了，
Because he was going to go to the South with a couple of friends
他_始在相s了。
and they started dating.
他跟他f只想为去，
They told him they wanted to go alone
所以他]e的地喝ザ燃倭恕
so he had nowhere to go on vacation.
昨晚就l信息告V我，好幔
Text me when you finish
我把上周和今天的蟪杲o你。
I left you your pay for last week and today.
我了解那些典作者多一些，美漫家。
I know the classic ones more
- 像@。      - Α
- Like this one. - Yeah.
{\fs48\pos(914
我爸爸有所有的米_・R{拉的漫和Fierros志全套。
My dad had all of Manara's comic books and Fierro's.
- 真酷。     - 是的。
- That's cool. - Yes.
是小孩r，我就常奈野帜抢锬砜矗因...
I used to take them from my dad when I was a kid
那上面有很多赤身裸w的人。看得我常性^。
There were naked people in them. They would really turn me on.
起初我以槊琢_・R{拉是主角呢，
At first I thought Milo Manara was the name of the main character
大些了我才意R到只是作者的名字。
but when I was older I realized it was the name of the artist.
{\fs48\pos(984
事上，《Déclic》是他最知名的漫
Actually
我知道的最好的作品。
Well the one I know the best.
是P于......一男人在一女孩身上b了O洹
It was about ...a guy who had put a device in a girl.
他按下b控器就她性高潮迭起。
and he'd click a remote control that would make her have orgasms.
他一按下b控器她就高潮。
He'd click it and she'd have an orgasm.
他偷Q她，直太。
And he'd spy on her. It was amazing.
人@不已。
It blew your mind.
事上，我我爸爸，拿碓倏匆槐椋
Actually
了，了
It's crazy... crazy.
在W校r，我常很多的超英雄。
When I was in school
一天，我的一些朋友做了本s志。
One day
是本校@s志
是校@s志，像非鹘ys志。
It was a magazine for the school
了解
Yeah.
一天他叫我做身漫。
And one day they asked me to do a two-page comic.
我不得不干了所有活骸
I had to do everything...
L，Π...
The drawings
整漫，知道幔
The whole comic
- 出版了幔                   - 出了。
- And did they publish it? - Yeah.
- 太酷了！ - 是，挺酷的。
- That's cool! - Yeah
能看到你的作品出版。
To see your work published.
是的，我做了些...
Yeah. And what I would do was...
我^去常用e人的一c材料，
I used to use other people's material a little...
{\fs48\pos(1070
H上，我大部分改自短篇小f，
Actually
像科塔_
like Cortazar's.
真害！
Cool!
_很酷，因槎际浅英雄，
It was cool
但具有更多超F主xL格...
but with a more surrealist style...
比如人物的背景。
Like the characters' background.
Γ就像粢樱很酷。
Yeah
人@。
Amazing.
你想睡了幔
Do you want to go to sleep?
是...好的。
Yeah... Okay.
嘿，里W
Hey
里W...
Leo...
里W，去你自己床睡。
Come on
so的，里W。
@家伙是做同拥氖隆
This guy always does the same thing.
好吧，我就下撬去了。
Okay
- 明天。 - 好。
- See you tomorrow. - Alright.
瓜_？
Guada?
嗯。 - 出什么事了？
- Yeah. - What's the matter?
她想要我陪她去派Γ
She wants me to go with her to the party
才不是，我了解她。
But that's not it. I know her.
她嫉妒了。
She's jealous.
她我是不是有女孩在。
She asked me if there were any girls here.
我f]有女孩^恚她不相信我。
She doesn't believe me when I say that no girls came over
]你的朋友怼
none of your friends.
我在W斯坦德（比利r沿海城市）待了很棒的2周，
We spent two great weeks in Ostende
她不明白，我F在不想和她待在一起，
but now she doesn't understand that I want to be with you guys.
不意味著我就不想和她在一起了。
It's not that I don't want to be with her.
她很好，你知道的。她真的很N心，
She's great. You know her. She's really sweet
可她真的很不安，
but she can be really insecure
我神o。
and it gets on my nerves.
我知道我有缺c，
I know I have my flaws
可我不嫉妒。
but I don't get jealous.
你不把注意力放到她身上。
You shouldn't pay attention to her.
是她的}，兄弟。
It's her problem
她自己去lX，即使很人。
Let her figure it out
你要做什么？回布宜Z斯艾利斯？
What are you going to do? Go back to Buenos Aires?
你被搞得心┮y的，也]法放松。
You're going to get upset and you won't be able to relax.
因樵谶@里你和我待著]}。
Because you're fine here with us.
你獐了，你打起怼
So you're going to be pissed off and you guys are going to fight.
托米...
Tomi...
e想了
Forget it.
e忘了你遇她r和露西在一起呢。
Don't forget that you met her when you were with Lucia.
所以她X得害怕和不安是很自然的。
So it's natural that she'd be scared and insecure.
是，我知道，但...
Yeah
我真的鬯。
I really love her.
不能和她在一起我死的。
I'd die if I couldn't be with her.
嘿，伙
Hey
赫曼真的很怪。
German's pretty weird.
我去M房g，他正在翻他的包。
I just went into Fer's room and he was going through his bag.
我不信你，老兄。你常造故事。
I can't believe you
M南多和那家伙一起^很多年了。
Fernando and that guy have been training together all year.
M告V我他很信任他。
Fer told me he really trusts him.
就在于你是混蛋吧，
You're just a cocksucker
所以你才杜撰@些事出恚我懂你。
So you make things up. I know you.
你看迭戈就在翻我的包。
Look at Diego going through my bag.
@是你的包？
Is this your bag?
嘿，你什么T恤淼模
Hey
我能借一件幔
Can I borrow one?
得^后o我。
But give it back to me later.
前滋炷愦┑哪羌是我已找了好久的\由馈
The other day you were wearing a sweatshirt of mine that I had been looking for for a long time.
Γ你就笑吧，我f真的。
Yeah
我就是喜g你的衣服。
I just love your clothes.
好了，ey翻我|西了。我o你找。
Okay
- 行，行！          - e再翻我|西了。
- Alright
- 好...  - 我不喜gy翻。
- Alright... - I don't like it.
o你。
There you go.
xx。
Thanks.
真的很y不令我心。
It's really hard for me not to get upset.
]人能比他更快，伙！
No one's faster than him
@家伙太有效率了。
The guy's effective.
他不必做什么花哨的幼鳌
He doesn't have to make any fancy moves.
@人很直率，他很巍
The guy's straightforward. He's simple.
那就是他是最佳的原因。
That's why he's the best.
是，可你之前一直都fR拉多{是最棒的。
Yeah
F在你看了灼采L就...
and now because you read a couple of interviews...
Γ我_看了灼采L，
Yeah
可我仍然看了他比的
but I've also watched him
他不像其他人，不在R^前作秀。
and he doesn't put on a show for the cameras like the rest.
他直接、迅速。
He's simple and quick
@是世代的}。
and it's also a generational thing.
r代了。
Times have changed.
我不同意那些白Vf他在外M球得分，
And I don't agree with the idiots who say he scores goals abroad
- 热鲂菜。          - 可就是。
- and here he sucks. - Yeah
那诱f的都是白V。
People who say that are idiots.
你不X得？
Don't you think?
- 伙，沓孕└恻c吧。          - 太爽了！
- The guys are here with pastries. - Awesome!
- 伙好幔 - 不e！
- How are you guys? - Cool!
可好？
What's up
你不相信街角l生的事故。
You wouldn't believe the accident there was around the corner.
- 太可怕了。 -真的？
- It's awful.  - Really?
是的。
Yeah
- 出啥事了？            - 。
- What happened? - A crash.
嘿，M，明天我去哪里？
Hey
我不知道，你想去哪海
I don't know. Wherever you guys want?
我可以去中央有泳池的夜...
We could go to that nightclub with the pool in the middle
人可以е一身衣服下水是吧。
that the guy fell into with all his clothes on.
或者我可以去首都，
Otherwise
然后晚上回怼
and come back at night.
你了幔孔我去首都？
Are you crazy? You want us to go to the capital?
去近c旱牡胤剑
Let's go somewhere nearer
不然M和里W不_去的，
otherwise Fer and Leo won't be able to drive
他什么都不能喝。
they won't be able to drink anything.
回淼r候我差c斓簦你想我跟前滋煲幔
Do you want us to come back wasted like the other day
嘿，我又不危U。
Hey
我可再也不喝酒了。
I don't drink anymore.
Yeah
莫Zf她牟幌胱邸
and Mono says she never wanted to have sex.
所以我不清楚。
So I don't know.
- 我有姨是蕾z。         - 是帷
- I have an aunt who's a lesbian. - Yeah.
她f，如果你真的是p性俚脑，
She says that if you're really bisexual
你不X得阂肿晕有什么}，
you have no trouble repressing yourself
因榧热荒阃r喜g女人和男人，
because since you like girls and guys
你遇一男人，]P系，
if you meet a guy
你可以和他在一起，然后去找一姑娘M足自身需求。
you can be with him and then go satisfy your needs with a chick.
那]什么的，很尉鸵种谱×恕
It's no big deal. It's easy to repress.
你就把他放在原地，就是那印
So you just leave him there and that's it.
他是第一要Y婚的人，
He's going to be the first to get married
- o他是不是基佬。  -Γ或S。
- whether he's gay or not. - Yeah
我еY物在c祝，
And we're going to be there celebrating it with presents
在他的婚Y上跳舞。
dancing at his wedding.
_。
It's true.
你知道我厶}米...
You know I love Romi...
可...我不能φ椅L床蔚呐孩f不啊。
but I can't say no to girls who call me for sex.
前滋焯}米有些文工作要完成，
The other day
她就去自己家睡的，
She went to sleep at her house
因殡x她隔天要去的那地方近一些。
because it was closer to where she had to go the next day.
她就像女巫似的。
It's like she's a witch.
我不知道@女孩是不是能通`...
I don't know if this girl is psychic or what...
娜塔莉o我l信息了。得娜塔莉吧，那w瘦的女孩？
Natalia texted me. Remember Natalia
得幔磕瘦女孩？
Remember? The skinny girl?
你不相信你F在看到的，托米。
You wouldn't believe what she looks like now.
她L了很多肉，脖子也粗了。天哪！
Man! She's got a lot more meat on her bones and a great rack.
我搭了程去她家，
I took a cab and went to her house
我干了九小r（Excuse me?!）。
and we fucked for nine hours.
那然，要不然我怎么k？
Of course. What was I supposed to do?
很自然的事。
It's natural.
然后我回到家，洗澡...
Then I got home and took a shower...
我感X糟透了。
and I felt like shit.
我X得很染巍
I felt really guilty.
透了
It sucks.
重要的是}米]抓住你，
The important thing is that Romi doesn't catch you
不然你想⒘四阕约旱摹
because then you'll want to kill yourself.
嘿，我X得赫曼有些像基佬。
Hey
你想知道是否他是。就去了解他啊。
You'd know if he was for sure. It takes one to know one.
e弄了。
Stop it
嘿
Hey...
你整天叫我混蛋。
You keep calling me "cocksucker" all day long.
混蛋，混蛋，混蛋。
"Cocksucker
你]X察到，但很┤恕
You don't realize it
我受蛄恕
I'm sick of it.
另外，我有女友。
Plus
你]意R到我只是在_玩笑。
You don't realize I'm just kidding around.
嘿，站住！我第一淼模
Hey
迭戈，我要用下你的洗l水，它太棒了。
Diego
好
Okay.
M，我要磉@合澡。
Fer
R淘窍掠昧茉。都洗了一小r了。
because Lucho's using the shower downstairs and he takes an hour.
好！
Alright!
你在看什么？
What are you reading?
《I》
"Hunger..."
挪威的。
It's Norwegian.
我要M砹恕Ｄ氵要洗幔
I'm going in now. Are you gonna take much longer?
不，要洗就M戆伞
No
傻逼混球！
Son of a bitch!
我要打得你屁L尿流！
I'm gonna kick your ass!
快c，伙！
Come on
十年是十一年的r候，我真的hh欲仙了。
We were in tenth or eleventh grade and we were really stoned.
那是第一次我集w。
It was one of the first times we all smoked together.
我在...
We were in...
Fatso的奶奶家
Fatso's grandma's house...
的院子里。我差c就M了她奶奶的房g。
in the yard. At one point I went to his grandma's room.
她最近去世了...
She had died recently...
我看里W在那...
And I saw Leo there...
和M，在房g里H帷
and Fer
我是孩子，而且都了。
We were just kids and we were stoned.
并且，我得探索一下，Π桑
Besides
不，我可不J槲是在H幔老兄。
No
我完全得，我就是在H帷
那是我的p性r期。
It was my bisexual phase.
F在我完完全全就是基佬。
Now I'm totally gay.
e，等一下子。我真不得那了。
No
我X得我一定是神志不清了，所以才幻想出@些淼摹
I think we must've been so stoned that we imagined it
但也就@恿恕
but that's all
每人都做他想做的事。
Well
就像胡安f的，越多基佬在，
It's like Juan says
留o我的女孩就越多。
the more girls there are for us.
Serrano：阿根廷Córdoba省纫市
前滋Fatso和我在Serrano。
他牧恕
and he was totally freaking out.
“@地方M是基佬，混蛋！”
"This place is full of gay people! Cocksuckers!"
胡安f“放松，Fatso”。
and Juan said "Take it easy
@里的基佬越多，
The more gay guys there are
留o我可x的女孩就越多。
the more chicks there are for us to choose from."
就是那印
That's how it is.
上次我...
Last time we were...
我不明白那些人，他J橹灰M到同性倬瓢衫铮
I don't get people who think that if you go to a gay bar
所有的基佬都上硖舳耗恪
all the guys are going to hit on you.
才不是。
It's not true.
比起女人恚基佬玩欲擒故v更多。
Gays play hard-to-get more than girls.
我l誓@是真的。
I swear it's true.
前兹哲铰和我去了派Γ
The other day Flor and I went to a party
{\fs48\pos(1002
M是同性俚谋勇≈髁x者...你缘盟是激M分子吧？
full of gay Peronists... You know she's an activist there?
嗯~
我盯著最基的那家伙看，穿著@身r衣。
And I looked like the gayest guy in there
我v真的。根本]人砀我搭。
I'm serious. No one gave me the time of day.
他焊翰豢茨恪＞褪悄印
They don't even look at you.
等等
Wait...
好，可是，你F在在哪里？
Okay
是，很明@，兄弟。
Yeah
Γ可就待在加油站，一半小r我就到。
Yeah. But stay thereat the gas station. I'll be there in half an hour.
行幔
Okay?
好...好的，老兄，好！
Yeah... Alright
R克西
Maxi...
R克西，跟我去接Fatso。
Maxi
他和胡安。那女孩把他甩你在那里了。
He's with Juan. The girls left him there.
他去了另一派Α
They went to another party.
R克西...
Maxi...
咋了？他做了？
What? Did they have sex?
Fatsof他做了。他在浴室上了她。
Fatso said he did. He screwed her in a bathroom.
胡安]能。他只和她在院子里H崃讼隆
But Juan didn't. He just made out with her in the yard.
so的，兄弟，我走。
Come on
- 我累死了，老兄。 - 快c，多替e人著想些！
- I'm exhausted
e┪遥兄弟！
Stop bothering me
- so的，so！ - 好！
- Come on
走了。
Let's go.
著，F在你到外面去玩足球，
Listen
Andrea泶撸好帷
and let Andrea clean up
]}，但是M德在躺著，他有c不舒服。
Okay
他不K事的。
But he won't get in the way.
之，她不用打吣情g房就行了。
In any case
然可以，]}。
Of course
{眼睛那男孩是l？
Who? The boy with the blue eyes?
赫曼，我一跆拳道的朋友。
German
他磉^我家状巍Ｄ阋^他吧？
He came to our house several times. You've seen him
^，可我不知道他是不是e人的朋友。
Yeah
不是，他是我朋友。但是我他一人怼
No
因樗就要和一些朋友去南方了，
Because he was going to go to the South with a couple of friends
他_始在相s了。
and they started dating.
他跟他f只想为去，
They told him they wanted to go alone
所以他]e的地喝ザ燃倭恕
so he had nowhere to go on vacation.
昨晚就l信息告V我，好幔
Text me when you finish
我把上周和今天的蟪杲o你。
I left you your pay for last week and today.
好
Okay.
- 你好幔Andrea？  - 是，一切都不e。
- Are you alright
- 你知道我a了吧。           - 嗯哼~
- You got my number
好的
Okay.
你可以o我打未接黼，如果你想的，那...
You can send me a missed call if you want
我打o你的。
I'll call you later.
我有孩子，知道吧？
I have two kids
我x婚了，可е珊⒆印
I'm separated
o我C，我成橐好爸爸。
I can be a good dad if you give me a chance.
他叫什么？
What are their names?
R卡斯和曼~。
Lucas and Manuel.
- 6q和4q。 - 好名字。
- Six and four. - Nice names.
出界！
Out!
可海
Damn it!
靠！
Fuck!
- 胡安... - O？
- Juan... - What?
再卷一根。
Roll another one.
可最多只蛞蝗顺榈摹
But there's only enough for one more.
赫曼
Ger...
你不是有朋友在附近，他有大麻吧？
Didn't you have a friend who's staying near here who had weed?
Yeah.
他就在附近...
He's near here...
20分路程h。
Twenty minutes away.
他些恚我乃那里I下。
Tell him to bring some and we'll buy some from him.
不用，他些恚]P系。
No
他有一大把草。
He has a bunch of plants.
他挺酷的。
He's really cool.
他也是子。
And he's totally out of his mind.
嘿，伙...
HEY
我明天早c去I肉吧，
Let's go buy meat early tomorrow
滋烨拔到那里晚了，什么都]了。
because the other day we got there late and there was none left.
嘿，M，要去幔
Hey
- 好的，去。  - 好。
- Yeah
嘿，R趟著了。
Hey
我照些他的照片。
Let's take some pictures of him
然后l到群里。
and post them for the group.
什么群？
What kind of group?
庇隆主x者的群？
A Peronists group?
是的。我常拍R痰恼掌。
Yeah. We always take pictures of Lucho.
嘿，M...
Hey... Fer...
我f真的。
I'm serious.
明天很早我就要把你叫醒。
I'm going to wake you up early tomorrow.
e熬太晚了。
Don't stay up too late.
想怎么著S你。
Well
明天我很早叫你起淼摹
But I'm waking you up early tomorrow.
行。假如我不起床你就跳到我身上。
Okay
拜~
拜
Bye.
他老是蚺R幔
They're always playing pranks on Lucho
Yeah.
可他是他里^最的。
But he's the worst of them all.
有夏天，胡安照了他。
One summer
扔到Fatso的包里。
taking a dump in Fatso's bag.
他不在乎。
He didn't care.
M德拿著他的手C_始拍照。
Fede got his cell phone and started taking pictures.
一年后，M德lF了照片，他想⒘怂。
And one year later
但他常像那娱_玩笑。
They always pull pranks like that
有r就玩^^了。
Sometimes they cross the line.
今天你也放衣服去洗了？
Did you put some clothes in the wash today too?
是
Yeah.
我]多的干妊了。
I don't have any clean underwear left.
o所^了。
It doesn't matter.
我就@么上床了。
I'll just go to bed like this.
我看你在看
I saw you reading "Demian."
你看很多。
You read a lot.
我自己就常看，
I do quite a lot of reading myself
可你看得比我多。
but I think you beat me.
不是。我只在度假r看。
No
一年里...
During the year...
我都]rg看。
I don't have time to read anything.
挺y的。
It's really hard.
你知道我_始做什么了幔
You know what I started doing?
棒O了。我外出不背背包，
It's great. I go out without a backpack
只б槐。
and with a book.
所以]了背包，我就拿在手里。
So since I don't have a backpack
我在地F上，公上或者做一些文案工作r，
When I'm on the subway
我就x，我就是那雍芸熳x完的。
I read them and that's how I finish them quickly.
所以...
So anyway...
{\fs50\pos(1122
《德米安》怎樱
What about "Demian"?
你以前x^幔
Had you read it before?
x^
Yeah...
可我看M去之后才lF，
but I started looking into it and I found out
{\fs50\pos(1104
是黑塞的故事。
that it's Hesse's story.
是他自己的故事。
It's his story.
你知道他F中做了什么?
Actually
{\pos(964
他用主角辛克R的名字出版了。
He published the book with the name of the main character: Sinclair.
他f是P于他自己的故事。
And then he said it was about him
所以他_始用黑塞的P名沓霭妗
so they started to publish it as "Hesse."
我已看了《荒原狼》
I had already read Steppenwolf and...
{\pos(988
和...
And...
跟佛陀有P的
the one about Buddha...
《悉_多》
Siddhartha.
{\pos(1032
是的，《悉_多》。
Siddhartha
另外，我x的r候才14q。很久以前了。
Besides
所以感X就像再x了一遍。
So I felt like reading it again.
我...
When I...
看它的r候，
When I read it
我X得他凵系旅装擦恕
I thought he was in love with Demian.
Γ有c那幼印
Yeah
我完全凵纤了。
I'm totally in love with her.
我要娶她。
I want to marry her.
我不在乎她嫉妒心l作。
I don't really mind her fits of jealousy.
我能掌控住。
I can handle it.
只要我不o她猜忌的理由，
As long as I don't give her reasons to be suspicious
不去y想，
and start imagining things
我X得她能克服掉的。
I think she'll get over it.
- Γ我缘媚阆g她。     - 是的，我鬯。
- Yeah
可她一直我是不是有女人在@里。
But she keeps asking me if there are women here
是不是有姑娘要^硗妗
if any girls are going to come over.
她f可能不期而至。
She said she's going to drop by unexpectedly.
- 你不知道啥r候。      - 我不知道。
- You don't know when. - I don't know.
她可以^戆。有}幔
She can come. What's the problem?
我不清楚...
I don't know...
但，不管怎...
But anyway...
她可不蠢。
She's not dumb.
她明白有女人r不r淼模
She knows that there are going to be women here sometimes
所^你的朋友啊。
friends of yours.
Yeah.
但我X得我]o她任何理由岩桑
But I think that if I don't give her any reason to be suspicious
她就_始松懈了。我不知道是不是。
she'll start to relax. I don't know.
我完全理解她。
But I totally understand her.
楹危
Why?
因樗的前男友和她朋友出欺_了她。
Because her ex boyfriend cheated on her with her friend.
天啊！
No!
- 太混蛋了！ - 不奇怪！
- What a jerk! - No wonder!
- 她精神受^。    - 然。
- Now she's traumatized. - Of course.
她很疑趾退在一起的人欺_她。
She's paranoid that the person she's with will cheat on her.
@就是槭裁此一直o我打我。
That's why she asks me all the time and calls me.
- 那家伙是混球。 - Γ他是混球。
- But the guy's an asshole. - Yeah
她朋友也是。
And so is her friend.
她一
Her too.
一婊子！
What a bitch!
- 我X得你不S附和。 -Α
- I think you shouldn't play along. - Yeah.
正_
Right.
我只想找女朋友，所以我再也]能w到“河豚式膨”了。
I'd just want to have a girlfriend so I don't get the blowfish anymore.
@段子不e。
That's was a good one.
梗不e
That's a good one.
啥？
What?
河豚似的！
The blowfish!
你真可怕。你喜g射在里面，兄弟。
You're terrible. You love to cum inside
f是J真的，e笑。
I'm serious
一天某人去到你家，
One day someone's gonna go to your house
夜深了，T起。
late at night
f“胡安，@是你孩子”。
and say "Juan
“孩子，@是你父H。你得照他。”。
Kid
你想⒘俗约旱模
You'll want to kill yourself!
老兄，祝你好\。f些什么呢？
Knock on wood
我的，可你得照好你自己。
I will
他f得Α
He's right.
是的，伙。戴套再做。
Yeah
我去把M叫醒。
I'm going to wake Fer up.
好的，好的。你要咖啡幔
Alright
好的，要。我R上下怼
Yeah
M...
Fer...
嘿
Hey.
M...
Fer...
嘿！
Hey!
起砹恕
Wake up.
so，我去I些肉！
Let's go buy some meat. Come on!
嘿，M！
Hey! Fer!
so的，老兄，起床了！
Come on
快c，你@混蛋！起砹耍快c！
快c，我要跳到你身上了，s快的！
Come on! I'm going to jump on you! Come on!
快c，混蛋！
Come on
s快，嘿，M！
Come on! Hey! Fer!
嘿！
Hey!
好了。
Okay
我在窍碌饶恪
I'll be waiting for you downstairs.
快，混球！
Come on
阿赫，你在里^幔
Ger
在
Yeah.
- 迭戈吵醒你了？              - 是的。
- Diego woke you up
那好。我要和他去物，
Okay
回碓僖，好幔
and I'll see you later
好
Okay.
你好
Hi.
身w可好？
How are you?
旅行如何啊？
How was your trip?
嗨。你在@干什么，甜心？
Hi. What are you doing here
你看起碚婷馈Ｗ约阂人淼模
You look beautiful. Did you come here by yourself?
不是，我和卡拉一起淼摹
No
和卡拉？
With Carla?
你]生獍桑
You're not mad
我不知道，。我太困了，我睡骸
I don't know
你太美了。
You're so beautiful.
我砹四愀吲d幔
Are you happy I came?
我真的很困，。e我那}。
I'm really sleepy
鹘o我！
Pass it to me!
在蛳...
Under the bridge...
是最好的
It's great.
我能告V你我的想法...
I can tell you what I think...
嘿，M
Hey
赫曼怎么了？
What's up with German?
什么怎么了？
What do you mean "what's up"?
我不知道，你告V我。
I don't know. You tell me.
我X得你看上去是很好的空手道搭n。
I think you guys look like you make a good karate duo.
我看上去就像那些O度渴望要孩子的人，
We always look like the ones who are desperate to have kids
但那是因槟能在自己的人生里Sr生孩子，我s不行。
but that's because you guys can have kids your whole lives and we can't.
比如，我表哥和姐姐是在算。
For example
你花一年rg去和某人s，
You take one year to meet someone
赡耆ハ嗵熟悉，
two years to get along well
三年搬到一起住。
and three years to move in together.
可感情]成，你又回到原c，
But if things don't work
然后你就浪M了三年人生。
and then you've wasted three years of your life.
我不知道。
I don't know.
事是你男人可以生孩子，
The reality is that you guys can have kids
和你遇的第一女人，在任何年o。
with the first woman you meet at whatever age.
你能在50q要孩子，如果你和一年p女人在一起的。
You can have a kid at 50 if you're with a young woman.
番茄居然在孩子的事宜。
Tomas' face talking about kids.
不，不。比起她f的，我了更多。
No
我f我趁F在年pr候把孩子生了。
I say we should have them now when we're young.
可她想去上W，Π桑
But she wants to go to school and all that
It's true.
如果我Q定的，F在我就要孩子。
If it were up to me
F在！
Now!
去年我和我男友徒步背包去了南部旅行，
Last year
去了Rincón del Azul，你知道幔
to Rincón del Azul. Do you know it?
- 知道。 - 棒O了！
- Yeah. - It's great!
那里有很多避y所，你可以待在里面，
Because there are refuges in that area where you can stay
想待多少天都可以。
for as many days as you want.
那里的水是青G色的。那地方直太了。
The water there is turquoise. That place is amazing.
你知道哪些地方必得去幔
You know where you really have to go?
去南方，整南部地^...
To the North
Purmamarca
我有一大堆那些酒店的系方式。
I have a bunch of contacts at the hostels there.
你想要的，我o你a，
If you want
- 把所有的信息lo你。                - 行，好的。
- and send you all the information. - Okay
我真想要看的地方，即使很昂F，
What I really want to see
那地方是智利。我渴望著去那里。
is Chile. I'm dying to go there.
我想去Pucén和Villarica。
I want to go to Pucén
然后去Valdivia。
and then go down to Valdivia.
我是孩子的r候和父母去^。
I went there when I was a kid
可我不得了。
But I don't remember anything.
我得一售~市觯
I remember a fish market
那里的海{，躺在光下。
and the sea lions that were there
人投食o他。
People would feed them.
要我F在就把WhatsApp的a告V你幔窟@泳筒忘了。
Do you want me to give you my WhatsApp number now so we don't forget?
- 行。  - 好幔
- Okay. - Yeah?
你好！
Hi!
你在干嘛呢？
What are you guys doing?
不，磉@骸Ｎ在狂g！
No
好的。把露莉和你所有人都叫上^怼
Okay
房子很大。
The house is great.
Mf我可以待在他母H房g。
Fer said we can all stay in his mom's room.
是的...我和M德、迭戈、R克西...
Yeah... We're with Fede
Yeah.
他就是你在森特{里W公@^的人。得幔
They're the guys you met at Centenario Park. Remember?
他一c都不┤恕Ｎ液涂拉在@里...
They're not annoying at all. I'm here with Carla...
我玩得非常_心。
and we're having the best time.
最_心的日子。
The best time.
戆桑真的很有趣。
Come on. It's a lot more fun.
真的，房子很大，他o我留了扇gP室。
Really
住手！
Stop it!
好
Okay.
行
Alright.
住嘴！
Shut up!
好的，拜。
Alright
咋樱咋樱
Well? Well?
他不怼
They're not coming.
我了解他。他不淼摹
I know them. They're not gonna come.
槭裁茨阋恢蹦\不停，Fatso？
Why did you have to whisper all the time
我只是f我有W球龊陀境兀
I just said we have a tennis court and a pool!
他到你f的了，Fatso！
They heard you
托R斯...
Tomas...
我拿走牙刷了，行幔
I'm taking the toothbrush
安眠。
Sleep well.
想去睡了幔
Do you want to go to sleep?
好的，睡吧。
Okay
你仍然有ο螅
Are you still in a relationship?
是的
Yeah.
- 你也是？        - 是。
- You too
H上我正在考]搬到一起住。
We're actually thinking about moving in together.
真的？
Really?
我也是。
So are we.
但我才_始@件事。
But we're just starting to talk about it.
可是很重要的一步。
But it's a big step.
Yeah.
有些像浣Y婚的幼印
It's kind of like getting married.
- 我不知道... - 可很好。
- I don't know... - But it's cool.
我不清楚@拥降缀貌缓谩
I don't know if it's cool to think about it like that.
可真的，我不知道。
But yeah
那你忠于感情幔
So are you faithful?
M我可能。
As much as possible.
我斫行阉。
I'm gonna wake him up.
eee，e那印
No
- 拜托！ - e，他不醒的。
- Come on! - No! He won't wake up.
- 好！     - 行，你想怎泳妥霭伞
- Yeah! - Okay
他老是霸占e人的床。
They always take your bed.
我怎么k？
What do we do?
我可以睡你的床。
We can sleep in your bed.
行
Okay.
你睡在@^好幔
You sleep on the side of the wall
P簦
turn off the lights?
好
Yeah.
M...
Fer...
- 嘿，老兄...                 - 什么事？
- Hey
砗臀一起吃些糕c。
Come with me to get some pastries.
R涕_走我的和瓜_的朋友去首都了。
Lucho took my car to take Guada's friend to the capital.
那就走路去吧。
Just go on foot.
不不。拜托老兄！d我去吧。
No
走路去，很近的。
Just go on foot. It's really nearby.
是我去。你兴廊肆耍
I always go. You guys are so lazy!
我和你去。
I'll go with you.
怎么樱
What happened?
那妞喊O了！
The chick's amazing!
我靠著W球鲇H帷
We were making out next to the tennis court.
有一刻她看著小屋，f“那是什么”。
At one point
就那印
And that was it.
她拉下我的子，_始吸我的u巴...
She pulled down my pants and started sucking my cock...
太爽了！
It was awesome!
然后我去P室拿安全套，
Then I went to the bedroom to get the condoms
@白Vs不o我。
and this idiot didn't want to give me any.
e...
Nah...
可我J檫@姑娘很忠\，
But I thought the girl was really faithful
至少瓜_f的是。
or at least that's what Guada says.
或S因樗都在各自交往中，她不介意。
Maybe since both of them are in a relationship
要是R]告V我他看到的鼍暗脑，
But if Lucho hadn't told me that he saw it
我是不相信的。
I wouldn't have believed it.
槭裁茨阋O我，你混蛋？
Why were you spying on us
如果我看你，一定打得你哭爹喊娘。
If I had seen you
我是J真的。
I'm serious.
那可不Α
That's not right.
你上的那妞菏俏遗萘艘幌挛绲某晒，
You screwed the girl I'd been flirting with all afternoon
用我的套子...
with my condoms...
至少我能看下她怎么做。
The least I could do was watch her in action a little.
你常f里W是混蛋，
You always say Leo's a cocksucker
但是你s看著她吸著我的u巴。
but you were watching her suck on my cock.
ΓΓ你混球。
你@Q淫癖B。
You perverted voyeur.
你有疑幔
What's the matter with you?
我都要尿到身上了。
I'm pissing myself.
你不跟我幔
Are you coming with me?
嘿，M是好κ郑Π桑
Hey
我不抗。
We don't fight.
我只。
We just train.
M是最棒的，每人都鬯。
But Fer's the best. Everyone loves him.
他Bn都不害。
He wouldn't hurt a fly.
我是小孩r，出去跳舞。
When we were kids and we went out dancing
有好状挝和e人打起怼
a couple of times we got into fights with people.
可他一直站在我@。
But he was always there for us.
他是保l我。
He'd always defend us...
任何人。他是第一出肀Ｗo@人的。
Anyone. He was always the first one to defend anyone.
太可惜了...
It's too bad...
他凵狭宋遗朋友的一朋友。
he's head over heels in love with a friend of my girlfriend's.
很久了，可他依然壑她。
It's been ages
我四曾成撼砑s。
The four of us used to double date.
我一起去度^假。
We went on vacation together once.
自哪枪媚镫x_他后，他就]再和e人^。
But since the girl left him
了。
It's crazy.
- 他]告V你？      - ]。
- Didn't he tell you? - No.
]，我不缘谩
No
他深壑她。
Yeah
他甚至都不那女孩，知道幔
He doesn't even talk
他]跟你f，可我了解。
He didn't tell you
我了解M，
I've known Fer for a long time
我知道他深壑。
and I know he's in love.
就算他]提她。
Even though he doesn't mention her.
他狂地壑她。
He's crazy about her.
如果那女孩想回到他身，
If the girl wanted to get back together with him
他毫不q豫的。
he wouldn't think twice.
you can be with him and then go satisfy your needs with a chick.
那]什么的，很尉鸵种谱×恕
It's no big deal. It's easy to repress.
你就把他放在原地，就是那印
So you just leave him there and that's it.
他是第一要Y婚的人，
He's going to be the first to get married
- o他是不是基佬。  -Γ或S。
- whether he's gay or not. - Yeah
我еY物在c祝，
And we're going to be there celebrating it with presents
在他的婚Y上跳舞。
dancing at his wedding.
_。
It's true.
你知道我厶}米...
You know I love Romi...
可...我不能φ椅L床蔚呐孩f不啊。
but I can't say no to girls who call me for sex.
前滋焯}米有些文工作要完成，
The other day
她就去自己家睡的，
She went to sleep at her house
因殡x她隔天要去的那地方近一些。
because it was closer to where she had to go the next day.
她就像女巫似的。
It's like she's a witch.
我不知道@女孩是不是能通`...
I don't know if this girl is psychic or what...
娜塔莉o我l信息了。得娜塔莉吧，那w瘦的女孩？
Natalia texted me. Remember Natalia
得幔磕瘦女孩？
Remember? The skinny girl?
你不相信你F在看到的，托米。
You wouldn't believe what she looks like now.
她L了很多肉，脖子也粗了。天哪！
Man! She's got a lot more meat on her bones and a great rack.
我搭了程去她家，
I took a cab and went to her house
我干了九小r（Excuse me?!）。
and we fucked for nine hours.
那然，要不然我怎么k？
Of course. What was I supposed to do?
很自然的事。
It's natural.
然后我回到家，洗澡...
Then I got home and took a shower...
我感X糟透了。
and I felt like shit.
我X得很染巍
I felt really guilty.
透了
It sucks.
重要的是}米]抓住你，
The important thing is that Romi doesn't catch you
不然你想⒘四阕约旱摹
because then you'll want to kill yourself.
嘿，我X得赫曼有些像基佬。
Hey
你想知道是否他是。就去了解他啊。
You'd know if he was for sure. It takes one to know one.
e弄了。
Stop it
嘿
Hey...
你整天叫我混蛋。
You keep calling me "cocksucker" all day long.
混蛋，混蛋，混蛋。
"Cocksucker
你]X察到，但很┤恕
You don't realize it
我受蛄恕
I'm sick of it.
另外，我有女友。
Plus
你]意R到我只是在_玩笑。
You don't realize I'm just kidding around.
嘿，站住！我第一淼模
Hey
迭戈，我要用下你的洗l水，它太棒了。
Diego
好
Okay.
M，我要磉@合澡。
Fer
R淘窍掠昧茉。都洗了一小r了。
because Lucho's using the shower downstairs and he takes an hour.
好！
Alright!
你在看什么？
What are you reading?
《I》
"Hunger..."
挪威的。
It's Norwegian.
我要M砹恕Ｄ氵要洗幔
I'm going in now. Are you gonna take much longer?
不，要洗就M戆伞
No
傻逼混球！
Son of a bitch!
我要打得你屁L尿流！
I'm gonna kick your ass!
快c，伙！
Come on
十年是十一年的r候，我真的hh欲仙了。
We were in tenth or eleventh grade and we were really stoned.
那是第一次我集w。
It was one of the first times we all smoked together.
我在...
We were in...
Fatso的奶奶家
Fatso's grandma's house...
的院子里。我差c就M了她奶奶的房g。
in the yard. At one point I went to his grandma's room.
她最近去世了...
She had died recently...
我看里W在那...
And I saw Leo there...
和M，在房g里H帷
and Fer
我是孩子，而且都了。
We were just kids and we were stoned.
并且，我得探索一下，Π桑
Besides
不，我可不J槲是在H幔老兄。
No
我完全得，我就是在H帷
那是我的p性r期。
It was my bisexual phase.
F在我完完全全就是基佬。
Now I'm totally gay.
e，等一下子。我真不得那了。
No
我X得我一定是神志不清了，所以才幻想出@些淼摹
I think we must've been so stoned that we imagined it
但也就@恿恕
but that's all
每人都做他想做的事。
Well
就像胡安f的，越多基佬在，
It's like Juan says
留o我的女孩就越多。
the more girls there are for us.
Serrano：阿根廷Córdoba省纫市
前滋Fatso和我在Serrano。
他牧恕
and he was totally freaking out.
“@地方M是基佬，混蛋！”
"This place is full of gay people! Cocksuckers!"
胡安f“放松，Fatso”。
and Juan said "Take it easy
@里的基佬越多，
The more gay guys there are
留o我可x的女孩就越多。
the more chicks there are for us to choose from."
就是那印
That's how it is.
上次我...
Last time we were...
我不明白那些人，他J橹灰M到同性倬瓢衫铮
I don't get people who think that if you go to a gay bar
所有的基佬都上硖舳耗恪
all the guys are going to hit on you.
才不是。
It's not true.
比起女人恚基佬玩欲擒故v更多。
Gays play hard-to-get more than girls.
我l誓@是真的。
I swear it's true.
你得把留o你，是吧？
You have to leave the car to your Mom
是，因樗要用。
Yeah
^何湍阏理。
We'll help you clean up later.
你待到明天幔
Are you staying till tomorrow?
Yeah.
我和你一起整理的。
I'll clean up with him.
我一夯怼
We'll be back in a while.
等阂。
See ya.
走吧。
Go.
- 你想去幔            - 我走。
- Do you wanna go? - Let's go.
- 好了？ - 好了。
- Ready? - Yeah.
一，二，三
One
你玩得_心幔
Did you have a good time?
_心。太棒了。
Yeah... I had a great time.
我能吻你幔
Can I kiss you?
{\b1\pos(960